[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which condition is described as a fear of cats?", "correct_answer": "Ailurophobia", "incorrect_answers": ["Cynophobia", "Pedophobia", "Alektorophobia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Godzilla (1984) was released in the U.S. as Godzilla 1985 and revived the series after nearly a decade.  What conection did this film have with the original U.S. release of Godzilla?", "correct_answer": "Raymond Burr returned as the American reporter.", "incorrect_answers": ["Both films feature new American scores by composer John Barry.", "They are the only two films in the series in which Godzilla is shown dead.", "The same American voice actors returned thirty years later to overdub the Japanese dialogue."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does the diet of ostriches consist of?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Insects", "Seeds", "Grass"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In this 1946 movie, set during Christmas time, Harry Bailey said the following about his brother, played by James Stewart: To my big brother George - the richest man in town!", "correct_answer": "Its a Wonderful Life", "incorrect_answers": ["White Christmas", "Somewhere in Dreamland", "The Gift of the Magi"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The name of which Native American group is also a name of an open source organization?", "correct_answer": "Apache", "incorrect_answers": ["Iroquois", "Navajo", "Cherokees"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the greatest depth the shell of a nautilus can withstand before imploding?", "correct_answer": "800 meters", "incorrect_answers": ["100 meters", "300 meters", "187 meters"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which list contains the three species of Zebras?", "correct_answer": "Grevys zebra, plains zebra, mountain zebra", "incorrect_answers": ["gray zebra, red zebra, plains zebra", "mountain zebra, savannah zebra, southern zebra", "Garveys zebra, Darwins zebra, gray zebra"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Complete the title of an 80s song by Duran Duran: \nNew Moon on...", "correct_answer": "... Monday", "incorrect_answers": ["... Thursday", "... Friday", "... See ya soon!"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is Andrews last name in the movie The Breakfast Club?", "correct_answer": "Clark", "incorrect_answers": ["Clay", "Dickinson", "Sutherlin"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Figs are a natural source of potassium and carbohydrates.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these characteristics makes Saturns moon Titan unique among all moons in the solar system?", "correct_answer": "It is the only moon to have a dense atmosphere.", "incorrect_answers": ["It is the only moon that is considered a captured object.", "It is the only moon with active volcanoes on its surface.", "It is the only moon to have a retrograde orbit."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "People having this type of allergy may have allergic reaction to bananas.", "correct_answer": "Latex allergy", "incorrect_answers": ["All of these", "Dust allergy", "Pollen allergy"]}]